In this material I will tell you how we can create an Austin extension that will allow us to search
currents. In many go such engines I will use Austin handbook and as you can see we have some addresses
here like the most popular good channel search engines. I will use Lingofer. Lingofer is like a extension
of a chrome. So if you go there is the chrome webster and the extension that will extract all
the other URLs. Press extract all links. I will use domains. So these are domains that you can use
for searching. We can only see manually as well. They copy it over. So I will use a scraper that we
just go through it. But I will just use this one obviously. It will just show all of the domains.
And I will copy here. And now we are ready. I will just call basically to the cursor and ask about
creation. I will just use the agent mode. I will use the plan mode. And for the plan mode
and here we can add the extension, we can add context. Remember that we can do it specifically
smooth images here. Possibly to connect the browser tab. And as well we can just paste all the links.
I will use only accept this because I know it's just not the one. So this is like a good search.
I want you to create a Chrome extension that will use this search engines.
I need a context. In go when I press right mouse button. Then be able to pick any of these
search engines and paste that text. All right. So first I will ask for a plan. If we prepare
a next move, then we will be able to create a multi-search engine extension. Okay, that's interesting.
All right. And how should the results open? I will say a new tab.
I need to open it in a new tab. If no text itself should happen,
change query. And prompt to enter query when we select any text.
So if someone just select a blank space, it will just prompt a query.
All right. Having installed preparing and I will install a directly from here.
We see at the Chrome extension that adds a musical auto model. So I won't quite
just be recommended for a most task. We see the essential snippets for manifest because I'm
creating a Google Chrome extension. It will create a menu in background JavaScript handle clicks
with prompt fallback. All right. So you have a five to do list. So to create a manifest,
implement the background service at engine lists. We've read me in one of the selections.
So you have a five task and I'm going to use it now. So I'll pause the video. Now it will just
build extension based on two loads that we have prepared. All right. As you can see, it has been
created. We see the manifest JSON. So we have a list of it. And start as marks. We have a manual
task. So now we can allow this impact version. So to do it, I will go to Chrome extension.
And now I just go to manage extension. I will use load impact. I'll send searcher
and it has been added here. All right. And now let me type it. So now it's great that it creates
we see possibility. I'll open a random news hacking news here. So one is suspiciously lowering
very slow. All right. Maybe it was my connection. So let me find like a some stat that we can
just look. So this is the overall touch. We have a by project. We have 18 dependencies. And now
we have search with. And you have full of the patterns that we have added. Actually, I think I
have to do should remove the device to by do. As you can see, it's search in the chain is right. That's
great. And there was like a ask. It's adding appendices. That's great because we just build like
extension very quickly about searching the stuff. So I think it's a great stuff. And now
I don't think it will work on LinkedIn, but maybe it will link. Try to look for some dependencies.
This actually is just searching for a job, but I think it's still great idea to create
maybe extension to search for a job or something like that. But as you can see, it works. Maybe
I will just try another website and maybe I will go to how ancient people sold themselves. We can
try it to look for some stuff like Pompeii. And now if I search with and I will try to look for
Korean, for example, never it would just look. So that's great. And if I go again and search with
Google, it would just look for a Pompeii in Pompeii. So it's literally in Italy. I have a polish
language here, but you see how it looks like. And then we can extend that extension. Thank you,
but you might, if I don't press anything and press Cask, enter search query. So it will just pop
up. And if I want to search, basically Derek here, I can just try to type like quantum. And if I
press enter, it will basically go there. So it's great. Even if we don't mark anything, we can quickly
search by it. And there are obviously two possibilities. Maybe if you'll select like a blank space,
maybe you don't want to have this visibility here, but having it still great because, for example,
it's fastened to open a new tab. So if you're like looking for some LinkedIn, you will be able to
look faster. That's great. Okay. That's it for it. We create a simple extension. It's not complicated
and it spits up our productivity. Keep that in mind that you can even add more like databases,
maybe looking for a job, looking for some marketplace. And then you can create your own database
and populate that Chrome extension. And if you go extend some of this functionality because
it's a great example, how we can create and speed up the process and add and create our new
extension. So I just ask, can you look at the engines? I think I had the platform that is not the
biggest search engine. I will use the green mode. And it's basically detected. It's LinkedIn,
because it's not a platform. So it recommended me to replace LinkedIn with that go and option
and the Yahoo. So now what I can do, I can even in ask mode, please.
Remote LinkedIn and replace it with that go and add Yahoo.
So it just probably go to the creation list. If not, we'll just switch the mode because
as you can see, ask it in the green mode. So if you're just updating mode.
All right, here's the exact edit to make a link. So this way, it's still here.
We see how we can add manually. So this way, you can just type. And to maybe make itself
familiar, I will just remove it. And obviously we can ask him to create, but we can add some
manual. And if I go to my extension tab, and if I return, it will reload. I will open a new tab
again. I'll open maybe this one, lecture magazine, and Photoshop is a Raspberry P. And if I search now,
there is no LinkedIn, but there is Yahoo. And there is even the Yahoo and the Go. I don't see it
here. Oh, it's here. And it was such for Raspberry P. Very simple. And we made it ourselves.
So I would just go to agent now and make a last fix for that. I don't like the one thing,
because if I open it up here, it's basically, it's not alphabetically. So I want you to reorder
engines, alphabetically. So it will basically change the order and it will make us to make
a little better. So we check the current background. Now I'm using agent. So it will apply results.
But yeah, we just tried to ask and ask only tasks how we can add something, but it will never
conduct any operation. So it's the main difference. And now if I go back,
and go to extension, and then go again to Raspberry P with this one,
as you can see, it has been reordered alphabetically. That's great. Okay, so this is it.
I might add some features in one of the next videos, but this is actually a great start,
because we have created a simple extension that will allow us to create fast search and
this is common for us intos. And keep that in mind, if you don't mark anything, and you want to
search for like that, go like security, you have a query. So this is like a simplified stuff,
and you do automatically search. And for the list, what I'm going to do, I will use cloud,
and I will use extended thinking. For free version, we have like a free per one week, I think,
but I will use the one now. I want you to create a list of all popular search engines
categorized by country. And I want you to avoid this. I will use them to create a Chrome
extension, that will search when we hover on a country tab. So this is my prompt, and we can
I think we don't need any connectors. We can have a normal style, and we can upload some
files, take a screenshot, but I think this will be a now, because only it is a web search and
extended thinking, it will just prepare like a model. It generated for us a list, I can copy it over,
I can always download the PDF file here, or as I'm already done, which is actually very good as
all, but I will just copy it over and obviously I have a context video. All right, it just copied
as this. So I cannot add another next, I cannot add this as extension, I will remove all of these things,
and this is the, I will just remove it cut. I want you to add a folder in the context menu
that will display search engines by country, leave the main search engines as it is.
Add a folder with the logs of search engines provided below. And now we'll just copy it
over and paste it. It's a long prompt, so you might take a few of the time, so here we see,
this is just a markdown from a cloud, but I think it will be able to actually create that.
All right, as you can see, it has been added. So now what I'm going to do, I'm going to
extension, open it up, manage extension, I'll press the fresh button, and as soon as it's refreshed,
let me go to and in the website, let me go here, and this is the button, I press R,
Serked, and by country. Now, as we can see, it has been added. So this way we can create our
Chrome extension, and maybe let me try to type it on Swiss cows. So the query item and search
does great. I'll try to maybe search programming. And here, I can search maybe by
Poland, W, B, P, L, programming, which is the query, and it looks great. It mostly aggregates.
The boy should have said, but still. And here's like a Swiss cows. And I will try last test,
some of the Philippines, Google, Malaysian. I'll try maybe
on the final account. We can move like specific Google because it's still great. And I will use
check Republic, says no, and it should work as it is. So it's programming, and I will be able to
and I'm able to use it. In check Republic, I see even the map, I see even check Wikipedia.
So that's great. It's our first project. I think it's great. We created a nice extension that allows us
to search dynamically here. I think we can remove that global as well and make it alphabetically.
So what I'm going to do, remove global from Suptap by country,
and all by country, sort of alphabetically. So this one will fix our issues. It's very fast.
So now I'm going to do the same. I'll go to my Chrome extension programming here,
and I'm going to refresh, go back to the page that we're looking for. So it's the UV. I will
close the thousand right, and I can just try to look for virtual environments.
Press right, search, and by country there is no global, and everything is alphabetically reordered.